[♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
This is my little brother,
George.
[SNORTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
[♪♪]
[PEPPA READS ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George
are going shopping.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Peppa and George
like shopping.
George loves sitting
in the trolley
[LAUGHS AND SNORTS]
[SNORTS]
So does Peppa.
Daddy, can I sit
in the trolley too?
[LAUGHS]
You're too big for the trolley,
Peppa.
Oh.
[SNORTS]
You can help with shopping.
Oh, goody.
[SNORTS]
We've got four things
on the list.
Tomatoes, spaghetti
onions and fruit.
I'll find it all.
[ALL LAUGH]
[SNORTS]
This way.
[GIGGLES]
Peppa and George love shopping.
Peppa, first we need tomatoes.
Hmm.
[SNORTS]
I can see them. I can see them.
Here are the tomatoes, Mommy.
Well done, Peppa.
One, two, three, four.
Now, put them
in the trolley.
[SNORTS]
I found the tomatoes.
Well done, Peppa.
Tomatoes. That's one thing
off the list.
What's next on the list?
Spaghetti!
"Paghetti."
That's right, George,
but it's called "spaghetti."
Paghetti.
Spaghetti is Peppa and George's
favorite food.
I wonder where
the spaghetti is.
I can see it!
This way.
Spaghetti.
Look, Mommy.
Here's the spaghetti.
Well done, Peppa.
Let's put the spaghetti
in the trolley.
Yes, Mommy.
[SNORTS]
Paghetti.
[LAUGHS]
George, it's called
spaghetti.
Paghetti.
[ALL LAUGH]
What's next on list, Peppa?
Crisps.
Crisps are not
on the list.
We have plenty of crisps
at home, Peppa.
DADDY PIG:
Have another guess.
Hmm.
I just can't remember.
Can you remember,
George?
Dinosaur!
Dinosaur?
George, there aren't any
dinosaurs in the supermarket.
[ALL LAUGH]
No, George.
The next thing on the list
is onions.
Onions!
I remember now.
Here they are.
[LAUGHS]
Well done.
One, two, three, four.
[LAUGHS]
[SNORTS]
Onions!
Very good.
That's nearly everything
on our list.
There's one last thing
on the list.
[SNORTS]
[GIGGLES]
A plant?
Is that on the list?
Oh, no, George.
The last thing
on the list is fruit.
Oh.
Never mind, George.
You can choose the fruit.
[LAUGHS AND SNORTS]
Where is the fruit?
Over there!
There are apples
and oranges
and bananas,
and a very big melon.
[SNORTS]
What fruit
shall we have, George?
Apples?
Oranges?
Bananas?
[SNORTS]
A melon!
[LOUD THUD]
[ALL LAUGH]
This is the checkout,
where all the food
is paid for.
Tomatoes.
Spaghetti.
Onions.
Melon.
Chocolate cake.
MOMMY PIG & PEPPA:
Chocolate cake?
Is that on the list?
Peppa, did you put the chocolate
cake in the trolley?
No, Mommy.
George, did you put
the chocolate cake
in the trolley?
No.
Well, I didn't put it in.
Then who did?
Uh...
I thought it might be nice
for pudding.
Daddy Pig!
[LAUGHS]
Naughty daddy.
Sorry. It just looked
so delicious.
It does look
rather yummy.
Oh, let's pretend
it was on the list.
Chocolate cake!
Hooray!
[ALL LAUGH]
[ROOSTER CROWS]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
It is Peppa's birthday.
It is very early
in the morning.
[SNORTS]
It's my birthday.
[LAUGHS]
George, wake up.
It's my birthday.
[YAWNS]
I'm going to have a party!
And Daddy is doing
a magic show.
[SNORTING]
Quick, George.
Let's wake
Mommy and Daddy up.
[SNORING]
Mommy Pig and Daddy Pig
are still fast asleep.
Wake up!
It's my birthday!
Oof!
[BOTH YAWN]
What time is it?
It's very late.
[TICKING]
It's 5:00 in the morning.
Yes. The whole day is going.
[LAUGHS]
Okay, let's get
your birthday started.
Yippee!
[ALL LAUGHING]
Mommy Pig, Daddy Pig and George
are giving Peppa
her birthday present.
BOTH:
Happy birthday, Peppa.
Ooh.
[RATTLES]
What is it?
[SNORTS]
A doll's dress.
I could put it
on Teddy.
Thank you,
everyone.
You're welcome,
Peppa.
I didn't know Teddy
was a girl teddy,
Oh, Daddy, of course Teddy's
a girl.
[SNORTS]
I love my new dress.
Thank you, everyone.
You're welcome, Teddy.
Don't get it dirty.
Do you know what's
happening next, Peppa?
Yes. My friends are coming
for my birthday party,
and Daddy is doing
a magic show.
[LAUGHS]
No one will know the magician
is your daddy.
You will introduce me as
the Amazing Mysterio.
"The Mazy Misty Oh"?
Yes, the Amazing Mysterio.
Daddy's been practicing
his magic tricks all week.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
My friends are here!
[LAUGHING]
Yippee!
Here are Peppa's friends.
Candy Cat, Suzy Sheep,
Danny Dog,
Rebecca Rabbit
and Pedro Pony.
Hello, everyone.
ALL:
Happy birthday, Peppa.
[ALL MAKING ANIMAL NOISES]
Come on, children.
The party is starting.
ALL:
Hooray!
Daddy Pig is going to do
a magic show.
Peppa, remember what
you have to say:
"Ladies and gentlemen,
introducing
the Amazing Mysterio"
Okay, Daddy.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Uh, it's magic daddy.
ALL:
Hooray!
[ALL CLAP]
For my first trick...
abracadabra!
[ALL GASP]
Wow! It's Teddy.
[ALL CLAP]
For my next trick,
I need a helper
from the audience.
ALL:
Me! Me! Me! Me!
[LAUGHS]
I just need one.
[SNORTS]
Young lady,
you put your hand up first.
Can you tell the audience
your name?
[BLEATS]
Suzy Sheep.
Okay, Suzy.
Here are three balls.
A red one, a blue one
and a yellow one.
Okay.
You have to secretly choose one
while my back is turned.
Okay.
Have you chosen one?
Yes.
Abracadabra.
You chose yellow.
No.
Uh, abracadabra.
Blue.
No.
Abracadabra.
Red.
Yes!
It is red.
ALL:
Hooray!
[ALL CLAP]
Silly magic daddy,
you said all three colors.
Shush, Peppa.
Don't tell anyone.
[ALL GIGGLE]
Would you like
one more trick?
ALL:
Yes, please.
Ooh!
DADDY PIG:
Close your eyes.
No looking.
Say the magic words:
"Abracadabra."
ALL:
Abracadabra.
Open your eyes.
Ooh.
Hooray!
My banana
birthday cake.
Blow the candles out, Peppa.
[INHALES AND BLOWS]
ALL:
Hooray!
Happy birthday, Peppa.
Thank you, everyone.
This is my best
birthday ever.
[ALL LAUGH]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Mr. Zebra, the postman,
is delivering a parcel
to Peppa's house.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Parcel for you,
Mr. Pig.
Thank you, Mr. Zebra.
[SNORTS]
Goodbye!
[HORN HONKS]
Look, I just got a parcel
in the post.
Can anyone guess
what's inside?
Dinosaur.
Oh, George.
You always say dinosaur
for everything.
[LAUGHS]
The parcel is far too small
to have a dinosaur inside.
Hmm, I think it's a...
a new toy!
You're very close.
I know what it is.
Your new camera.
A new toy for Daddy Pig.
That's right.
It's a movie camera.
[SNORTS]
We can make movies with it
and watch them
on our television.
Can I use it first,
Daddy?
[CHUCKLES]
It's a bit too difficult
for children to use.
Even I need to read
the instructions.
Hmm.
It's a bit harder
than I thought.
Suzy Sheep's mommy
has a movie camera.
She switches it on
like this.
[BEEPS]
Oh. Well done, Peppa.
CAMERA:
Thank you for purchasing
the Movie 3000.
[BEEPS]
I am eager
and ready to shoot
your first movie.
Is there a way
to turn off that voice?
I'm not sure.
[BEEPS]
Thank you for purchasing
the Movie 3000.
On Suzy's camera you just press
this button to stop it talking.
[BEEPS]
Thank you for purchasing--
Now it won't talk
anymore.
Well done, Peppa.
What shall I film first?
Film me!
[SNORTS AND LAUGHS]
Okay, Peppa.
[CAMERA BEEPS AND WHIRS]
Hello. I'm Peppa Pig.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
[BOTH LAUGH]
Come on, everyone.
[STATIC CRACKLES]
Hello. I'm Peppa Pig.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
[ALL LAUGH]
Again, again.
Okay.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
[SPED-UP AUDIO]
Hello. I'm Peppa Pig.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Again, again.
[SPED-UP AUDIO]
Hello. I'm Peppa Pig.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
[LAUGHS]
Again, again.
[CHUCKLES]
Maybe we should film
something new.
I know.
Daddy Pig
must leave the room,
and we'll make a movie
to show him.
This way.
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig has to wait in
the kitchen while Mommy Pig
Peppa and George
make a secret movie.
No peeking, Daddy Pig.
[LAUGHS]
[BOTH GIGGLING]
We all have to do
something.
George, do you want
to go first?
[SNORTS]
[CAMERA BEEPS]
[LAUGHTER]
[SNORTS]
Are you ready?
Can I come in
and see the movie?
MOMMY PIG:
Finished!
You can come in now.
George has made a movie,
and so has Peppa.
Let's see George's movie first.
[SNORTING]
Dinosaur. Grrr.
George is pretending
to be a dinosaur.
Grrr.
That's a very scary
dinosaur.
[ROARS]
[CRIES]
NARRATOR:
Oh, dear. George is frightened.
Don't be frightened,
George.
That's not a real dinosaur
on TV. It's you.
[ROARING]
Grrr. Dinosaur.
[ALL LAUGH]
Now let's see Peppa's movie.
Ho, ho, ho.
Who is that meant to be?
I am Daddy Pig.
Ho, ho, ho.
I see.
My tummy is very big,
because I eat
a lot of cookies.
[ALL LAUGH]
My tummy is not big.
[SNORTS]
But it is true
that I like cookies.
And the more you eat,
the bigger your tummy gets.
[ALL LAUGH]
Okay, what's next?
This is my sweet
little brother, George.
[SNORTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
This is me.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
And this is the real
Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS LOUDLY]
[ALL LAUGH]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa's playgroup are going
to put on a play.
The Little
Red Riding Hood.
ALL:
Hooray!
All the children have parts
in the play.
They have to practice
at home.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Peppa is going to be
Little Red Riding Hood.
Mommy Pig has made
her costume.
Daddy Pig is helping
Peppa practice.
[SNORTS]
Okay, Peppa,
what do you say?
I'm Little Red
Riding Hood.
Very good.
Then what?
Um...
I'm going to visit
my grandma.
I'm going to visit my grandma.
Bravo, Pepper!
[ALL CLAP]
Danny Dog is going to play
the Big Bad Wolf.
[BARKS]
Granddad Dog and Mommy Dog
are helping him practice.
I'm the Big Bad Wolf.
[LAUGHS]
Try not to laugh,
Danny.
You should be
a bit scarier.
Try it like this, Danny.
[CLEARS THROAT]
I'm the Big, Bad Wolf!
I'm going to eat you
all up!
[ROARS]
[SCREAMS]
[LAUGHS]
You see?
Yes.
That was really scary.
[GIGGLES]
Pedro Pony is going to play
the hunter.
[BLOWS HORN]
He will rescue Peppa
from the Big Bad Wolf.
Um, I'm the hunter.
And...
Pedro is a bit shy.
You say: "I'm going to chase you
away, you big bad wolf."
Um, go away,
naughty wolf.
[BLOWS HORN]
[LAUGHS]
Very good, Pedro.
Rebecca Rabbit is going
to be the grandma.
What do I say, Mommy?
Let's see.
At the start
of the play,
you get locked in a cupboard
by the Big Bad Wolf.
Then right at the end
of the play,
you are rescued
by the hunter.
And you say, "Thank you."
Ahem. Thank you.
Very good, Rebecca.
[LAUGHS]
[BELL CLANGING]
Everyone has come to see
the school play.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to our play,
The Little Red Riding Hood.
[APPLAUSE]
First, let us meet
the actors.
[ALL MAKING ANIMAL NOISES]
[CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING]
Please, please.
For the sake of the actors,
no photography, please.
And now our play begins.
[FANFARE PLAYS]
AUDIENCE: Ooh!
[APPLAUSE]
Grandma is at home.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
But who is this visitor?
[BARKS]
I'm the Big Bad Wolf.
Well done, Danny!
Um...
Oh, dear.
Danny has forgotten
what he says next.
"Grandma, you must go
in the cupboard."
[BARKS]
Go in the cupboard.
MADAME GAZELLE:
The Big Bad Wolf
is pretending
to be Grandma.
AUDIENCE:
Ooh!
[SNORTS]
I am Little Red Riding Hood.
I'm going to visit
my grandma.
Bravo, Peppa.
Daddy, you must not
take photos.
Oops. Sorry, Peppa.
Carry on.
Ahem, I'm going to visit
my grandma.
[LAUGHING]
Oh, you don't look like
my grandma.
What big eyes you have.
[GIGGLES]
What big teeth you have.
Grrr!
[GASPS]
You are not Grandma.
You are the Big Bad Wolf.
AUDIENCE:
Ooh.
Help! Oh, help!
[SNORTS]
MADAME GAZELLE:
But look who is here.
Just in time.
Pedro the Hunter.
Help. Oh, help?
MADAME GAZELLE:
Just in time.
Pedro the Hunter.
Pedro is a bit shy.
Pedro, would you like me
to come on with you?
Yes, please.
[BLOWS HORN]
You are a very
naughty wolf.
[LAUGHS]
I saved you, Grandma.
ALL:
Hooray!
[CLEARS THROAT]
Thank you.
Bravo! Bravo!
[CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICK]
MOMMY PIG: Bravo. Well done.
Pedro, you were
very good.
[GIGGLES]
[SNORTS]
You were almost
as good as me.
[ALL LAUGH]
[PEPPA LAUGHING AND SNORTING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING AND LAUGHING]